{
  "decks": [
    {
      "difficulty": 3,
      "tags": [
        "python",
        "django"
      ],
      "name": "python advanced",
      "description": "Awesome deck for learning python",
      "author": 1,
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "difficulty": 2,
      "tags": [
        "js",
        "html"
      ],
      "name": "js for learning basics",
      "description": "Awesome deck for learning is",
      "author": 1,
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "difficulty": 2,
      "tags": [
        "js",
        "react"
      ],
      "name": "js for learning advanced features",
      "description": "Awesome deck for learning js",
      "author": 1,
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "flashcards": [
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "JS question 1",
      "answer": "JS answer 1",
      "decks": 1,
      "category": "js",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 217,
      "tags": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 1
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "JS question 2",
      "answer": "JS answer 2",
      "decks": 1,
      "category": "js",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 2137,
      "tags": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "JS question 3",
      "answer": "JS answer 3",
      "decks": 1,
      "category": "js",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 217,
      "tags": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "JS question 4",
      "answer": "JS answer 4",
      "decks": 1,
      "category": "js",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 2137,
      "tags": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "Python question 1",
      "answer": "Python answer 1",
      "decks": 2,
      "category": "python",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 217,
      "tags": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "Python question 2",
      "answer": "Python answer 2",
      "decks": 2,
      "category": "python",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 2137,
      "tags": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "Python question 3",
      "answer": "Python answer 3",
      "decks": 2,
      "category": "python",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 217,
      "tags": [
        2
      ],
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "React question 1",
      "answer": "React answer 1",
      "decks": 3,
      "category": "react",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 217,
      "tags": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "React question 2",
      "answer": "React answer 2",
      "decks": 3,
      "category": "react",
      "difficulty": 1,
      "rating": 2137,
      "tags": [
        1
      ],
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "React question 3",
      "answer": "React answer 3",
      "decks": 3,
      "category": "react",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "rating": 217,
      "tags": [
        2
      ],
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "React question 4",
      "answer": "React answer 4",
      "decks": 3,
      "category": "react",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "rating": 217,
      "tags": [
        2
      ],
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "author": 1,
      "question": "React question 5",
      "answer": "React answer 5",
      "decks": 3,
      "category": "react",
      "difficulty": 3,
      "rating": 217,
      "tags": [
        2
      ],
      "id": 12
    }
  ]
}